[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Barnacles eat with their legs.",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Blue sharks are known to be not migratory.",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Butchart Gardens has 27 greenhouses.",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Canadian geese mate for life.",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "The original Capilano Suspension Bridge was built with hemp rope and cedar planks.",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Finfish are amongst the most cultured species in B.C waters.",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Giant Pacific Octopi are very extroverted.",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Gray whales are also known as devil fish.",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Grizzly bear front claws can grow to be a maximum of 5cm in length.",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Grouse Mountain Skyride goes to the peak of Vancouver.",
    "answer": true
  }
]
